<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide San Francisco</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="work_spaces">Work Spaces</string>
    <string name="stay_active">Stay Active</string>
    <string name="work_space_amazon_workspace">Amazon Workspace</string>
    <string name="work_space_amazon_workspace_address">Courtyard Entrance, 525 Market St 2nd floor, San Francisco, CA 94105</string>
    <string name="work_space_peets_coffee">Peet’s Coffee</string>
    <string name="work_space_peets_coffee_address">1400 Mission St Suite 130, San Francisco, CA 94102</string>
    <string name="work_space_coffee_cultures">Coffee Cultures</string>
    <string name="work_space_coffee_cultures_address">1301 Mission St, San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="work_space_arlequin_cafe">Arlequin Cafe</string>
    <string name="work_space_arlequin_cafe_address">384 Hayes St, San Francisco, CA 94102</string>
    <string name="staying_active_ymca">The YMCA</string>
    <string name="staying_active_ymca_address">855 Sacramento St, San Francisco, CA 94108</string>
    <string name="staying_active_planet_fitness">Planet Fitness</string>
    <string name="staying_active_planet_fitness_address">350 Sansome St, San Francisco, CA 94104</string>
    <string name="staying_active_yoga_to_the_people">Yoga to the People</string>
    <string name="staying_active_yoga_to_the_people_address">2973 16th Street, 5th floor, San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="title_activity_place_description">Place Description</string>
    <string name="place_description_ymca_description">We reopened our beautiful, newly renovated community space in 2010 and offer full-service health and wellness facilities, a salt-water pool, as well as robust youth, family and adult programs. We\'re an essential hub addressing health disparities in our community- join us!</string>
    <string name="place_description_planet_fitness_description">No matter what you’re looking for in a gym, we’ve got a membership option made for you. All Planet Fitness members enjoy unlimited access to their home club and the support of our friendly, knowledgeable staff anytime you need it. PF Black Card® members receive additional benefits, including the ability to bring a guest for free and access to any of our 1,600+ PF locations.  Looking for a little extra guidance or inspiration to help you meet your fitness goals? As a PF member, you can take advantage of our free fitness training or find your motivation by reading real member experiences on Planet of Triumphs.  It’s our goal to provide a clean, safe, welcoming environment for anyone who walks through our door, and all the equipment, amenities and support you need once you’re here.  Welcome to Planet Fitness. The Judgement Free Zone®</string>
    <string name="place_description_yoga_to_the_people_description">Located just by the 16th Street and Mission Bart stop, this was a highly frequented exercise stop for Founding Class students.  A donation based yoga studio, Yoga to the People offers a range of time options and a great workout for people with all levels of experience. If you don’t have a mat but want to give it a try, not to worry! Mats are available for rent at the studio, $2 // mat.</string>
    <string name="place_description_amazon_workspace">The AWS Lofts are a place where startups and developers can meet over coffee, work on their apps, attend educational sessions, and get in-person answers to AWS technical questions – all at no cost.  Gain hands-on experience through free technical workshops on serverless, containers, AI, machine learning and more. Or, sharpen your startup business acumen by attending best practice sessions that include fundraising and marketing. Plus, network and learn first-hand from other hot startups, VCs, and accelerators.</string>
    <string name="place_description_peets_coffee_description">For over 50 years, our goal has been to offer the best coffees and teas in the world, without compromise. We\'ve learned that one of the secrets to great coffee is the people behind it.\n\n<b>OUR VALUES.</b>\nMastery. Passion. Authenticity. Community. Ownership. Growth. We thrive in this purpose-driven environment. We explore and evolve, while standing firmly on our legacy and commitment to the craft of fine coffee and tea.</string>
    <string name="place_description_coffee_cultures_description"><b>THE COFFEE</b>\nWe believe Counter Culture Coffee is one of the best roasters in the U.S. if not the world. The product, the people, the branding and the practices all appeal to the way Coffee Cultures wishes to conduct business, as an industry leader. CCC reinforces our entire philosophy and how we want to separate our brand from the competition. CCC sources directly from farmers, and works with passionate coffee professionals always seeking to raise the bar. They know where the beans come from and it shows as they equip their clients with all of the tools needed to speak intelligibly about the product. We were the first retail account for CCC in California / on the west coast / in San Francisco. That\'s the Coffee Cultures strategy - to be an industry leader, with high quality beans / roast that you can\'t find anywhere else.\n\n<b>OUR LIFESTYLE</b>\nOur team and our customers matter. We are passionate about creating connections with our baristas and making each visit better than expected. The Coffee Cultures brand is built on authenticity, the finest ingredients, and the rich culture of this fascinating industry.</string>
    <string name="place_description_arlequin_cafe_description">Arlequin Cafe &amp; Food-To-Go is located in the Hayes Valley neighborhood of San Francisco, California. We serve artisanal sandwiches, salads, beverages and desserts at reasonable prices. Arlequin Cafe is connected to its next-door neighbor, Arlequin Wine Merchant, and wines by the glass or bottle are available to Arlequin Cafe patrons.</string>
    <string name="food_drink">Food &amp; Drink</string>
    <string name="food_drink_trader_joes_1">Trader Joe’s 1</string>
    <string name="food_drink_trader_joes_1_address">10 4th St, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA</string>
    <string name="food_drink_trader_joes_2">Trader Joe’s 2</string>
    <string name="food_drink_trader_joes_2_address">555 9th St, San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="food_drink_mi_tierra_market">Mi Tierra Market</string>
    <string name="food_drink_mi_tierra_market_address">2023 Mission St, San Francisco, CA 94110</string>
    <string name="food_drink_foods_co">Foodsco</string>
    <string name="food_drink_foods_co_address">1800 Folsom St, San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="food_drink_grocery_outlet_bargain_market">Grocery Outlet Bargain Market</string>
    <string name="food_drink_grocery_outlet_bargain_market_address">1245 S Van Ness Ave, San Francisco, CA 94110</string>
    <string name="food_drink_costco_wholesale">Costco Wholesale</string>
    <string name="food_drink_costco_wholesale_address">450 10th St, San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="food_drink_safeway">Safeway</string>
    <string name="food_drink_safeway_address">2020 Market St, San Francisco, CA 94114</string>
    <string name="place_description_trader_joes_1_description">Monday – Sunday 8am -9pm \n Trader Joe’s is a retail supermarket with a large selection and reasonable prices. Some items may be cheaper at Trader Joes than Safeway, although the selection at Safeway is often greater.</string>
    <string name="place_description_trader_joes_2_description">Mon -Sun 8am -10pm</string>
    <string name="place_description_mi_tierra_market_description">Mon -Sun 7:30am -8:45pm\nSmaller supermarket chain, great for cheaper fresh produce.</string>
    <string name="place_description_foodsco_description">Mon -Sun 6:00am -1:00am\nThis national warehouse grocery chain has cheaper prices on many groceries.</string>
    <string name="place_description_grocery_outlet_bargain_market_description">Mon – Sun 8:00am – 10:00pm\nEasily accessible by 24th St BART or MUNI Bus</string>
    <string name="place_description_costco_wholesale_description">Mon-Fri 9:00am-8:30pm, Sat-Sun 9:00am-7:00pm\nMembers-only (basic membership annual fee is $60) warehouse selling a huge variety of items including bulk groceries, electronics &amp; more. Most international Costco cards will work in the U.S. stores!</string>
    <string name="place_description_safeway_description">Monday – Sunday 24 hours everyday\nSafeway is a major retail supermarket with everything you may need, at reasonable prices which are cheaper if you have a membership card.</string>
    <string name="green_space">Green Space</string>
    <string name="green_space_mission_dolores_park">Mission Dolores Park</string>
    <string name="green_space_mission_dolores_park_address">San Francisco, CA 94114</string>
    <string name="place_description_mission_dolores_park_description">A Leave No Trace park, encompassing nearly 16 acres, Mission Dolores Park is one of San Francisco’s most popular destinations, the vibrant heart of its equally vibrant, culturally diverse neighborhood. Here you’ll find lush green lawns shaded by tall palm trees, a soccer field, six tennis courts, one basketball court, a multi-use court, a playground, and two off-leash dog play areas. Yes. Many festivals, performances, and other cultural events are held here, and on sunny afternoons people flock to the park to play, picnic, lounge, walk their dogs, and enjoy spectacular views of the city’s skyline and beyond.\\nNamed for nearby Mission Dolores, the park is situated on land that was once a Jewish cemetery. The City bought the property in 1905 and established the park. In 1906 it served as a refugee camp for more than 1,600 residents made homeless by the earthquake and fire.\\nMission Dolores Park is bounded by Church, Dolores, 18th, and 20th streets. The Muni Metro J-Church Line runs along its western edge.</string>
    <string name="green_space_yerba_buena_gardens">Yerba Buena Gardens</string>
    <string name="green_space_yerba_buena_gardens_address">750 Howard St, San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="place_description_yerba_buena_gardens_description">Embrace your every mood, find green relief and celebrate diversity amid landscaped lawns, serene waterfalls and colorful gardens at the cultural heart of San Francisco.</string>
    <string name="green_space_golden_gate_park">Golden gate park</string>
    <string name="green_space_golden_gate_park_address">San Francisco, California</string>
    <string name="place_description_golden_gate_park_description">Golden Gate Park is the third most visited park in the United States. While the park is free to visit during the day, popular attractions charge admission, such as deYoung Museum, California Academy of Sciences and Conservatory of Flowers. The park is filled with gardens, museums, art, flowers, trees, lakes, birds and wildlife. There are also plenty of opportunities to participate in sports, clubs and other activities. Browse the site for information on parking, maps, weddings, hotels, permits, making reservations, transportation, contact numbers, and the history of Golden Gate Park.</string>
    <string name="green_space_bernal_heights_park">Bernal Heights Park</string>
    <string name="green_space_bernal_heights_park_address">3400–3416 Folsom St, San Francisco, CA 94110</string>
    <string name="place_description_bernal_heights_park_description">Bernal Hill provides visitors with a breathtaking 360-degree panorama and clear views of San Francisco Bay, the Golden Gate Bridge, downtown, San Bruno Mountain, and the hills of the East Bay. These windswept slopes are still sunny when Twin Peaks is shrouded in afternoon fog. Red-tailed hawks soar overhead, the breeze sends waves undulating through the native grassland community, and visitors hike around the hill’s peaceful summit to escape from the complexities of urban life. As one of the few remaining natural refuges in San Francisco, Bernal Hill is a special place for the city’s human and wildlife inhabitants.  A paved limited-access road and a network of well-defined dirt trails wind around the hill’s flanks and provide access to the summit.</string>
    <string name="green_space_corona_heights">Corona Heights Park</string>
    <string name="green_space_corona_heights_address">Roosevelt Way &amp; Museum Way, San Francisco, CA 94114</string>
    <string name="place_description_corona_heights_description">This park has some of the best views in San Francisco, but don’t overlook the wonderful wildflower display that carpets the grasslands each spring. Among the flowers you may see here are checkerbloom, California poppy, footsteps of spring, Douglas iris, mule’s ears, and Johnny jump-up, a sensitive species that is the only host plant for the callippe silverspot butterfly. Also look for anise swallowtail, a big yellow butterfly with black shoulders that frequents San Francisco’s hilltops.</string>
    <string name="green_space_lands_end_lookout">Land’s End Lookout</string>
    <string name="green_space_lands_end_lookout_address">680 Point Lobos Ave, San Francisco, CA 94121</string>
    <string name="place_description_lands_end_lookout_description">At every turn of the trail on this wild and rocky northwestern corner of San Francisco, there is another stunning view. Along the way you’ll see hillsides of cypress and wildflowers, views of old shipwrecks, access to the epic ruins of Sutro Baths, pocket beaches, and a new Lookout Visitor Center. You can thank community volunteers who have helped revitalize and restore the native habitat here.  Volunteer with our Park Stewardship program to ensure that the landscape continues to thrive and support wildlife for generations to come.  Public Transportation is the best way to get to Lands End.</string>
    <string name="green_space_san_francisco_botanical_gardens">San Francisco Botanical Gardens</string>
    <string name="green_space_san_francisco_botanical_gardens_address">1199 9th Ave, San Francisco, CA 94122</string>
    <string name="place_description_san_francisco_botanical_gardens_description">Welcome to San Francisco Botanical Garden, a living museum within Golden Gate Park, offering 55 acres of both landscaped gardens and open spaces, showcasing over 8,500 different kinds of plants from around the world.  San Francisco Botanical Garden\'s Entry Garden. The Bay Area\'s mild temperatures, wet winters and dry summers, coupled with San Francisco\'s famous coastal fog, provide a range of climatic conditions that exist in few other botanical gardens in the world. These unique conditions allow it to grow and conserve plants from all over the globe, including plants that are no longer found in their native habitats.  With its unique microclimate, San Francisco Botanical Garden is able to recreate conditions of the high elevation tropical cloud forests of Central and South America and Southeast Asia. Rare high elevation palms as well as plants from New Zealand and temperate Asia also thrive here. Largely due to these natural advantages, San Francisco Botanical Garden is known for its unique, diverse and significant botanical collections. The extensive Magnolia collection, for example, attracting visitors with its dazzling display of winter flowers, is recognized as the world\'s fourth most significant collection of Magnolia for conservation purposes, and the most important outside China*, where a majority of Magnolia species are found.</string>
    <string name="green_space_twin_peaks">Twin Peaks</string>
    <string name="green_space_twin_peaks_address">501 Twin Peaks Blvd, San Francisco, CA 94114</string>
    <string name="place_description_twin_peaks_description">At 922 feet in elevation, Twin Peaks is second only to Mt. Davidson in height, offers spectacular views of the Bay Area, and is a world-famous tourist attraction. Originally called “Los Pechos de la Choca” (Breasts of the Maiden) by early Spanish settlers, these two adjacent peaks provide postcard views and a treasure trove of animal and plant diversity. Most visitors to Twin Peaks drive (or take a tourist bus) to the north peak parking lot to enjoy 180-degree views of the Bay Area.  Many miss an opportunity to experience the coastal scrub and grassland communities of this 64-acre park. Similar to the Marin Headlands, Twin Peaks gives us an idea of how San Francisco’s hills and peaks looked before grazing and then development changed them forever. The vegetation is primarily a mix of grassland and coastal scrub. Expect strong winds as you hike among plants such as coyote brush, lizard tail, pearly everlasting and lupine.  The endangered Mission Blue Butterfly has adapted to the strong winds and flies low to the ground from lupine to lupine. Native plants provide habitat for brush-nesting birds like the white-crowned sparrow and animals such as brush rabbits and coyotes.</string>
    <string name="green_space_balboa_park">Balboa Park</string>
    <string name="green_space_balboa_park_address">San Francisco, California 94112</string>
    <string name="place_description_balboa_park_description">Ever changing. Always amazing.  Where culture, science, and nature collide, Balboa Park is home to more than 16 museums, multiple performing arts venues, lovely gardens, trails, and many other creative and recreational attractions, including the San Diego Zoo. With a variety of cultural institutions among its 1,200 beautiful and lushly planted acres, there is something for everyone.</string>
    <string name="green_space_buena_vista_park">Buena Vista Park</string>
    <string name="green_space_buena_vista_park_address">Buena Vista &amp; Haight Street, San Francisco, CA 94117</string>
    <string name="place_description_buena_vista_park_description">Buena Vista Park, located in the center of the city, is named for the spectacular views from its upper slopes. The oldest park in San Francisco, it features secluded, winding trails and one of the city’s few remaining coast live oak groves. Buena Vista’s natural area is on the park’s northern side.  Oak woodlands have always been considered special places, and many cultures have deemed the oak sacred. A world of creatures thrives among the shadows of an oak woodland. The acorn crop comes in the fall when other food sources dry up and many animals must put on fat for the winter. Several species of the birds known as sapsuckers drink from the trees’ phloem (vascular tissue that transports sugars throughout the tree), just below the bark. Western harvest mice strip the bark, and Botta’s pocket gophers eat the roots of saplings. Insectivorous bird species such as brown creepers and nuthatches scour the trunks, branches, and leaves for the many insect species that live in oaks.  Acorns from the oak trees are the main food source for squirrels. Some species of squirrels gather nuts for the winter and store them in any accessible hiding place, usually by burying them. Although squirrels generally have excellent memories for their caches, many an oak tree has gotten its start from a forgotten acorn.</string>
    <string name="place_image_description">This is an image of the place</string>
</resources>
